<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vegia</string>
    <string name="gemgive">Yes, hrrmmm. You a space gem I give. Your memories store it will help.</string>

    <string-array name="challenges">
        <item name="chal1">To make a vegan burger you have. A patty from beans or lentils should make. Recipes online you find and choose one you will. Yes, hrrmmm.</item>
        <item name="chal2">Scrambled tofu for breakfast make. Lots of seasoning and herbs use.. Hmm.</item>
        <item name="chal3">I sense the dark side in you. You are tempted to give in. You will make pancakes to give yourself some comfort. Flax egg you should use. Yes.</item>
        <item name="chal4">Make Thai summer rolls you must. Rice paper wrapper you should use.</item>
        <item name="chal5">Tacos today make. Beans and walnuts instead of meat use. Hrmmm.</item>
        <item name="chal6">A pizza today with nutritional yeast instead of cheese we will make. A vegan pizza dough you can use, if you must. Yes, hrrmmm.</item>
        <item name="chal7">For this challenge, sushi you will make. Fried eggplant or zucchini instead of salmon you will use. Yes.</item>
        <item name="chal8">Hrrmmm. Challenging this one is. Make a mezze platter you must. Hummus from scratch you will make. Yes. Various vegetables you can use. Hrrmmm.</item>
        <item name="chal9">Wraps today will be. Fill them with falafels and vegetables you will . Vegan wraps you must buy and on falafel recipe decide.</item>
        <item name="chal10">Pasta pesto you will make. The type of pasta you can pick, but pesto yourself must make. Cashews and herbs you will use. Yes, hrrmmm.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tips">
        <item name="tip1">Hrrmmm. Adding flour or oats can help the burger together stick.</item>
        <item name="tip2">Turmeric and paprika powders the yolk-like color can create. Yes.</item>
        <item name="tip3">If the flax egg too watery is, it stand for 5-10 minutes you should let.</item>
        <item name="tip4">Thin, see-through, all-tapioca papers you avoid. Easily they tear.</item>
        <item name="tip5">All the difference mushrooms and herbs make. Hrmm.</item>
        <item name="tip6">Nutritional yeast provides nine amino acids that your body can not make. Hmm.</item>
        <item name="tip7">Wasabi a better taste will give.</item>
        <item name="tip8">Nuts and berries more vitamins will provide. Hrmmm.</item>
        <item name="tip9">A binding ingredient it together can help keep. Hrmmm.</item>
        <item name="tip10">Nutritional yeast a parmesan can replace. Hrmmm.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
</resources>